Christopher Metcalf

Software Engineer

27 Park Ave, Northwood, NH 03261 **Cell: (603) 325-3698** <u>cmetcalf2022@gmail.com</u>

https://github.com/C-Metcalf

SUMMARY

Proficient mid-level software engineer with a year of experience in designing, developing, and implementing software applications. Utilizing Django, C#, and PyQt to write simple, secure, and scalable code. Successfully redesigned the company's website, product line, in house software, and infrastructure.

EXPERIENCE

National Aperture Inc, Salem, NH — *Software Engineer*

October 2022 — present

Responsible for developing and implementing software applications

- Maintain and update legacy website
- Redesign website on WordPress
- Communications via UART, USB, I2C, SPI and CAN
- Front-end web development with Ruby on Rails & Tailwind CSS
- GUI App development for Raspberry Pi using Qt/Pyside6

Aldi, Concord — store associate

February 2020 – October 2022

- Coordinated with a small team to work efficiently
- Was recommended for manager position
- Worked with heavy machinery
- Handle large sums of cash daily
- Opened and closed the store regularly

Languages

Python

C++

C#

Ruby

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

Web Frameworks

Django

PyQt

Rails

DataBases

PostgreSQL

MariaDB

MySQL

EDUCATION

Associate's in Computer Engineering & Technology

January 2021 - May 2023, New Hampshire Technical Institute